<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>stem on Bits to Bytes</title>
    <link>https://bitstobytes.co/tags/stem/</link>
    <description>Recent content in stem on Bits to Bytes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy 2020 Bits to Bytes</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 13:56:52 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bitstobytes.co/tags/stem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Seed Called VidUp</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/aseedcalledvidup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 13:56:52 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/aseedcalledvidup/</guid>
      <description>When I first got into programming I was bewildered by the near infinite things one could accomplish through code. And like many people in the beginning, I struggled with the basic concepts. There was a strong sense of uncertainty within me at the time. I distinctly remember thinking, “Am I really cut out for coding? There’s other people way better than me already.”
This sense of uncertainty is normal for anyone learning a new skill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say YES!</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/sayyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 16:48:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/sayyes/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered what it would be like if you just started saying yes to life and all the opportunities that come your way? I know after watching the Yes Man movie (I recommend it!) when I was little I thought the prospect of embracing every experience sounded fun and exciting… yet I really did not realise where it would lead me!
Somehow I became a person who seemingly did so many things and ended up loving meeting people and embracing new adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sydney Hacks</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/sydneyhacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:18:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/sydneyhacks/</guid>
      <description>It was January 2020. I had just returned from NCSS in Melbourne and had won a hackathon at the Academy of Entrepreneurs. The energy of the camps lingered on me and I was itching to do something, something big, exceptional and meaningful to me. Now, almost every bit of knowledge I have around programming came from online courses. When the topics were easy, I cruised through the tutorials, but when my code stopped working, it was truly frustrating to figure out what’s wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Word from our Founder</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/awordfromourfounder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:18:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/awordfromourfounder/</guid>
      <description>Hey, everyone!
Developing Bits to Bytes has been a jam-packed journey for me over the past couple of months. The team and I have iterated over the idea several times, putting in hours of effort into bringing it to life.
Now as I type up this first post, I find myself teeming with excitement at the possibilities of what Bits to Bytes can grow into.
A strong passion for science, technology, engineering and maths has inspired me to come up with this idea.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>