<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>entrepreneurship on Bits to Bytes</title>
    <link>https://bitstobytes.co/tags/entrepreneurship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in entrepreneurship on Bits to Bytes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy 2020 Bits to Bytes</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 11:51:22 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bitstobytes.co/tags/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Part Two: Here is How to Taste Entrepreneurship</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/exploreentrepreneurshiptwo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 11:51:22 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/exploreentrepreneurshiptwo/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone!
After reading part one of this article, you are probably wondering how you can get started as an entrepreneur.
Though I am still young and learning, I believe there is four key steps you can take to get started:
Step One: Find something you like
Before diving into trying to capitialise on your skills, figure out what you are good at! Whether it&amp;rsquo;s technology, art, food, music, socialising or fashion, find something you are passionate about and enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part One: Here is Why You Should Explore Entrepreneurship</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/exploreentrepreneurship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 11:51:22 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/exploreentrepreneurship/</guid>
      <description>Youth is a springing blossom. It’s the perfect season of life to experience several of many firsts. First true friendships. First crush. First setback. First feeling of immense pressure as exams can creep up on you.
Entrepreneurship is commonly associated with money, exchanges of cash in the millions and talks of stocks and shares.
When in reality, being an entrepreneur really only entails two things. The most familiar to many is profit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>