<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Bits to Bytes</title>
    <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Bits to Bytes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy 2020 Bits to Bytes</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bitstobytes.co/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Code in School - Why Bother?</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/codinginschoolswhybother/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 19:20:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/codinginschoolswhybother/</guid>
      <description>I initially had no clue what to write about when starting this post.
So I figured I may as well think of why it is that I even like or got into programming in the first place.
The first thing that I realised that if it hadn’t been for the computer lab that was set up and a passionate temp teacher in primary school starting a makeshift coding club at lunchtimes, I probably never would have had an interest in computers or coding, never would have decided to continue teaching myself once she left the school, never would have paid attention in year 7 technology classes, and most likely would not have chosen IST as a year 9 elective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed, Lead, Instinct</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/speedleadinstinct/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 15:46:55 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/speedleadinstinct/</guid>
      <description>I first joined my schools F1 program in 2018 at the beginning of year 9. At the time I didn’t really know much the competition, and was only really joining to get an activity I could use for Duke of Ed. I already had a love for designing and making things and I thought making a mini race car sounded pretty cool. In my first year of competition I competed with a team called Quicksilver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Ninjas</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/codeninjas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/codeninjas/</guid>
      <description>The launch of the code club “Code Ninjas” founded by students Giuliana De Bellis and Edwina Adisusila in 2018 saw an exciting opportunity for extra-curricular computer programming at St Ursula’s College Kingsgrove.
Code Ninjas was first developed after Giuliana and Edwina attended the National Computer Science school in 2018. This camp inspired the girls to take their newfound passion and skills to the students at our school. Coming back from the camp, they brainstormed possible ways to get the college community involved in coding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bailey&#39;s Story</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/baileysstory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:18:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/baileysstory/</guid>
      <description>My love for stem came from meeting one of my best friends, Tom Day, back in 2016. He got me into computer programming.
This opened a whole lot of doors in opportunities for me, such as attending my first academic camp hosted by the National Computer Science School in 2019. Through this, I found a love for all things STEM! This camp was honestly one of the best experiences of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling for Physics</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/fallingforphysics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:18:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/fallingforphysics/</guid>
      <description>Throughout my early years of high school, I always intended to take either Biology or Chemistry as my science elective for the HSC. So when I wound up in a class studying Physics due to subject availability, I was not enthusiastic at all. I went in with many preconceptions about physics: that it was all about maths, that you needed to study engineering to understand the content, that my English-loving brain wouldn’t be able to comprehend anything&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Word from our Founder</title>
      <link>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/awordfromourfounder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:18:15 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitstobytes.co/posts/awordfromourfounder/</guid>
      <description>Hey, everyone!
Developing Bits to Bytes has been a jam-packed journey for me over the past couple of months. The team and I have iterated over the idea several times, putting in hours of effort into bringing it to life.
Now as I type up this first post, I find myself teeming with excitement at the possibilities of what Bits to Bytes can grow into.
A strong passion for science, technology, engineering and maths has inspired me to come up with this idea.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>